(Priya:)So did you get
to talk to Penny?
(Leonard:)Oh, yes.
Indeed, I did.
(Priya:)And?
(Leonard:)She completely understood
everything I said. Case closed.
(Priya:)Was she upset?
(Leonard:)Maybe, but that's
not my problem.
(Leonard:)She's not my girlfriend,
you are.
(Priya:)I hope you weren't
cruel to her.
(Leonard:)Is the autumn cruel
for letting the flowers die,
(Leonard:)or is that just nature's way?
(knocking)
SHELDON: Leonard?
(knocking) Leonard?
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
What?!
(Sheldon:)I think I figured out
Wolowitz's magic trick,
(Sheldon:)and I need you
to pick a card.
(Leonard:)I am not opening
that door, Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)As you wish.
(Sheldon:)Pick a card, put it back,
and prepare to be amazed.